Muhammad Irsyad Ashari

Mobile Software Developer | irsyadashari.github.io/myportofolio/

Email : muhirsyadashari@gmail.com

Phone : +6287880931606

LinkedIn : linkedin.com/in/irsyad-ashari-11a51812a/

Github : github.com/irsyadashari

An informatics bachelor and a proactive mobile developer with 1 year+ experience in Android and iOS application development. I have passions in mobile development field to create a scalable app with clean architecture to make people's life easier.

EDUCATION

Universitas Hasanuddin (UNHAS)

B.Sc. in Computer Science

Makassar, Indonesia

GRADUATED, JULY 2020

- Cumulative GPA: 3.59/4.0
- Others: Internet of Things and Parallel Computation Laboratory Assistant, Indosat Ooredo iOS Expert learning path (IDCamp), and XL Future Leaders Batch 7 Awardee

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT Carakde Solusi Informatika

Makassar, Indonesia July 2018 - August 2019

Project: ReViRe (Real Estate Virtual Reality)

Unreal Engine/Unity Software Developer - Part Time Contract

- Developing Mixed Reality (VR/AR) Based App in Real Estate to serve a new service where a real estate buyer candidate could explore the house they're about to buy with customisizing option to change the color of the wall, changing/moving furniture, etc.
- Serving presentation points to desctibe ReViRe to Investor Candidate in IBTle (Inkubator Bisnis Telekomunikasi Informasi dan elektronika) South Sulawesi events held by Indonesian Ministry of Industry

Project: dr. Bob Wahyudin Pediatrician Android & iOS Mobile App

Makassar, Indonesia

Mobile Developer (Android & iOS) - Full Time Contract

and Google Playstore named "Praktek Dokter Bob".

August 2019 - Desember 2020

- **UI/UX Research onsite (dr Bob's Clinic)** by doing inteviews with doctor's bob patient and nurse about parent's need to simpliify registration protocol in clinic easier.
- Developing Queue Information Android & iOS Based Application
 Using Android Studio and Kotlin as the main programming language collaborating with Android Jetpack for Activity Navigation and Testing for Android app and using xcode 12 and swift 5 as the main programming language and UlKit as the Interface Builder. Using popular third party libraries such Alamofire, Nuke, Charts, etc to use consume API and display the data in the iOS app and finally upload the apps in the iOS AppStore

Makassar Coding

Web Front-End Mentor - Part Time Contract

Makassar, Indonesia January 2021 - Present

Teaching basic HTML, CSS, JS and Bootstrap in exclusive class containing max 10 students. Presenting
how to solve programming problems the effective way and how to use control version to maintani web-app
in the long term

PROJECT SHOWCASE:









